astrogyan.com 2019-11-06

# User Member Privacy Policy Statement - Free Astrology, Indian Astrology, Free Horoscope Predictions Guide and Info Library

| |   

Our privacy policy is targeted at one central goal and that is to keep the information that we ask in our site "astrogyan.com" during registration. This statement is designed to clearly highlight our strong commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information collection and dissemination practices for our website as above:

Astrogyan.com's registration form requires users to give specific information (ie: name, date of birth, time and place of birth, e-mail address) and other demographic information (ie: preferred deity). We use this specific information to uniquely identify you as a unique user / member of this site as well as to desist minor's, who, by law, are prohibited from using this site. We also use the contact information from the registration form to send the user promotional material based on the options that the specific choice that the user has opted for. The user's contact information is also used to contact the user when necessary usually by email. That apart, we use access logs to track the usage trend to further improve upon the site for the benefit of the user. We also use cookies to track the user on a per session basis to present the user with content and information relating to his input and choice. We do not sell, trade, or rent the personal information to others. However, we may do so in the future with trustworthy third parties, but you can tell us not to do so - see the choice/opt out section below. Users may also choose not to receive future mailings, see -- the choice/opt-out section below.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the user's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they may be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is also used to help us understand market characteristics and trends. This information may be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis and will not include any personally identifying information.

Additionally, We use and record our users IP addresses as well as use cookies to help identify the user as a unique member of our site. Furthermore, the user's IP address is used to help identify the user, track their site usage pattern, understand what attracts the user back to the site, which modules are most preferred by the members, and to gather broad demographic information.

Please note, this site contains links to other sites in terms of advertisements, co-branding promotions, alliances etc... Astrogyan.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

By using this site you consent to the collection and use of this information by us for the purpose outlined above.

**Choice to Opt Out of Mailing Lists**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the user. This site gives users the option of not sending any promotional mails to them by letting them choose appropriately during registration itself.

**Dispute Resolution Statement**

At the best of our abilities, we do not forsee a cause or reason for dispute in the above mentioned privary policy. Yet, if any dispute does arise the same can be amicably solved betwwen both the parties by discussion and arbitration. At the maximum extent, the user is entitled to stop using our services if our privacy policy is not acceptable to the user. Further for existing users, we will take steps to remove all user related details from our records if so specifically requested by the user. But there after the user will not be able to access or use our services.

**Contacting Us at Astrogyan.com**

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with us at astrogyan.com you can contact our Customer Relations Manager for accurate and precise clarification of your questions.

| |
